<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<entry id="home">

	<config>
		<clear>true</clear>
	</config>

	<entry id="291211_zcms_12">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-12-29</date>
		</config>
		<title>
				<span>Zcms 1.2</span>
		</title>
		<content> 
			<span> <b> Zcms 1.2 is out</b>! This is the hardest release I've done so far.. most of the code
			was rewritten.</span>
			<br />
			<span>Changelog:</span>
			<br />
				<li>added a very basic documentation updated to Zcms 1.1.2, so it's quite useless ATM ^_^</li>
				<li>there is no more distinction between posts and comments, they're all entries</li>
				<li>added support for loading subentries and entry's content only when the they are shown</li>
				<li>Most configs are now inheritable to subentries</li>	
				<li>Now entries behaviour can be set. Available modes are: show everything, hide everything, and show only the first entry</li>
				<li>the homepage is not hardcoded anymore. It can be set in the config</li>
				<li>minor changes</li>
			<br />
			<b>KNOWN ISSUE:</b> Using slide animation will probanly produce glitching, use fade instead 
			<br />
			I've opened a github repo for the project. You can find it <a target="_blank" href="https://github.com/m3l7/Zcms">here</a>.<br />
			I will change the project name (zcms is the name of at least 2 other CMSs :| )
			<br />
			BRB.
			</content> 
	</entry>


	<entry id="291111_zcms_112">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-11-29</date>
		</config>
		<title>
				<span>Zcms 1.1.2</span>
		</title>
		<content> 
			<span> <b> Zcms 1.1.2 </b>! Another minor release</span>
			<br />
			<span>Changelog:</span>
			<br />
				<li>deprecation of old functions: xml2string</li>
				<li>add support for loading php or html files.</li>
				<li>&lt;load_xml&gt; and add_xml() have been renamed to &lt;load_file&gt; and add_file()</li>
				<li>the title element has been renamed to 'title' for a php incompatibility</li>	
			<br />
			Next version will have a better article/comment approach, using more server side functionalities.
			<br />
			<b>KNOWN ISSUE:</b> comments in the non-first articles are not shown...
			</content> 
	</entry>

	<entry id="8911_zcms_111" date="2011-09-08" author="m3l7">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-09-08</date>
			<load_file mode="LoadWhenShown" entryid="comments_8911_zcms_111">resources/comments/8911_zcms_111.xml</load_file>
		</config>
		<title>
				<span>Zcms 1.1.1</span>
		</title>
		<content> 
			<span> <b> Zcms 1.1.1 </b>! Bug fixing only release...</span>
			<br />
			<span>Changelog:</span>
			<br />
				<li>comments are hidden correctly when the parent&#39;s post is hidden</li>
				<li>all comments are loaded correctly now</li>	
			<br />
			<span>I want to release one or two versions of zcms before adding some server-side love... </span>
			<span>Some routines are becoming slow, I need to polish the code, add some little features (collapse/expand
				all comments), and think about the best post/comment approach..</span>
			<br />
			<span>Stay tuned.</span>
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry id="7911_zcms_11" date="2011-09-07" author="m3l7">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-09-07</date>
		</config>
		<title>
				<span>Zcms 1.1</span>
		</title>
		<content> 
			<span>Phew! Just released <b>Zcms 1.1!</b>. Finally I've added comments support. There are many bugs and limitations.. you are warned</span>
			<br />
			<span>Changelog:</span>
			<br />
				<li>added analize_config_post() for analize config after adding the content</li>
				<li>added support for aligning elements horizontally (useful with fixed positioned elements)</li>
				<li>initial support for comments</li>
			<br />
			<span>Known issues: </span>
			<br />
			<li>comments are not correctly hidden</li>
			<li>comments are read-only for now (server implementation of zcms is still non-existent)</li>
			<li>I don&#39;t know if comment&#39;s protocol should be rewrited, deleted or kept as it is now... 
			 using only posts, which can eventually be replies of other posts, seems a better and simpler idea</li>
			 <li>comments' animation doesn't work</li>
			 <li>comments are not loaded correctly when 2 or more entries are shown (ajax overlapping)</li>
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry id="6911_zcms_103" date="2011-09-06" author="m3l7">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-09-06</date>
		</config>
		<title>
				<span>Zcms 1.0.3</span>
		</title>
		<content> 
			<span>new shit online! <b>Zcms 1.0.3!</b>. Added a couple of nice features I'm sure you'll love</span>
			<br />
				<li>fixed animation (added an additional subdiv to every structure divs)</li>
				<li>added more animations. Now you can choose between fade,slide and hide(default)</li>
				<li>added subdiv &#39;text_right&#39;</li>
				<li>support for date and author (tag &#39;author&#39; and &#39;date&#39; for css styling)</li>
				<li>support for showing/hiding entries. By default, first entry is shown, others are hidden</li>
			<br />
			<span>Spread the love &lt;333 </span>
			<br />
			<span>lord_of_chaos=odites</span>
		</content>
	</entry>
	<entry id="5911zcms102" date="2011-09-05" author="m3l7">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-09-05</date>
		</config>
		<title>
				<span>Zcms 1.0.2</span>
		</title>
		<content> 
			<span><b>Zcms 1.0.2</b> up and running. This is (another) minor release including, among bug fixes:</span>
			<br />
			<li>animations are loaded serially (better stability)</li>
			<li>class names clean up (no more tons of useless classes inside the same div)</li>
			<li>the first entry now has an additional 'firstentry' class for more css fun</li>
			<li>xml tags has better names now (tab --> title, container --> entry)</li>
			<li>added a little parser that substitutes variables in the text entries</li>
			<br />
			
		</content>
		</entry>
		<entry id="2911first" date="2011-09-02" author="m3l7">
		<config>
			<author>m3l7</author>
			<date>2011-09-02</date>
		</config>
			<title>
				<span>Hello World (:</span>
			</title>
			<content>
				<span>Plaoo@all</span>
			</content>
	</entry>
</entry>

